## **ORIT LESHEM**

755 Dunboyne Cres' | London, ON | N5X 1X9 | 519-933-0408 | azmono@gmail.com Portfolio: Orit Leshem

#### **Profile**

A highly-motivated, goal-oriented full-stack developer specializing in JavaScript, Node.js, and React.js. With a combination of General Assembly's Software Engineering Immersive certification, Coding Academy's full-stack developer diploma, an MBA, and bilingual fluency in English and Hebrew, I am ready to make a meaningful impact in the InsurTech space.

## **Core Skills/Competencies**

- JavaScript
- Html
- CSS
- React.js
- Node.js
- Angular

- Vue.is
- Python
- Django
- Mongoose
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL

- AWS S3
- iQuerv
- GitHub
- Management
- Problem-Solving
- Flexibility and Innovation

## **Relevant Work Experience**

### **Full-Stack Developer Fellow**

Coding Academy, Tel-Aviv, Israel

November 2022 – February 2023

- Developed full-stack applications with a solid working knowledge of engineering frameworks, technology and tools like React.js, Vue.js, Angular, Node.js, and MongoDB
- Collaborated closely with team members to execute program specifications, adapting, integrating, coding, testing, and debugging programs with limited supervision.
- Demonstrated exceptional efficiency and effectiveness, consistently exceeding expectations and motivating team members to meet ambitious project goals.

## **Software Engineering Fellow**

General Assembly, Toronto, Canada

April 2021 – June 2021

- Developed full-stack applications using a working knowledge of specific domains and engineering frameworks such as React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Phyton, and SQL.
- Collaborated closely with team members on all aspects of application development from start to finish, executing program specifications with limited supervision.
- Consistently solved complex technical problems using routine procedures.

### Work Experience

### **Front Desk Supervisor**

September 2021 – September 2022

Idlewyld Inn & Spa, London, Canada

- Demonstrated exceptional customer service skills by effectively managing and resolving guest complaints, increasing customer satisfaction ratings.
- Implemented effective communication, resulting in improved customer service delivery.
- Utilized strong sales skills to upsell hotel services and amenities successfully.

# **ORIT LESHEM**

755 Dunboyne Cres' | London, ON | N5X 1X9 | 519-933-0408 | azmono@gmail.com Portfolio: Orit Leshem

## **General Manager**

January 2018 – January 2021

Kinneret-mall shopping center, Jordan Valley, Israel

- Created and executed sales strategy raising appraisal value by 14.7% over two years
- Transformed inner layout by 10% to accommodate two new Mega-retail stores
- Managed 40 properties to provide a first-class rate shopping experience
- Collaborated with the local municipality to provide catering solutions for 500 employees

## **Business consultant / Business development manager** Freelance, Tel-Aviv, Israel

**Emergency Medical Responder (EMR) and Ambulance driver** 

Magen David Adom (Israeli Red Cross first aid organization)

January 2014 – January 2018

2016 - 2021

- Co-Founded an Israeli Cyber services company, launched within three months of Founding
- Established and managed a Sales and services call center for Afikim Electric vehicles
- Built and trained sales and support teams and set up the IT service infrastructure.
- Consulted on HR management and sales training programs for small and medium privately held businesses

Education	
Coding Academy Israel, Full Stack Developer Coding Academy Israel, Canada, remote	2023
SEI Software Engineering Immersive, Full Stack Developer General Assembly, Toronto, Canada	2021
MBA Marketing and advertising specialization The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	2007
Bachelor of Business Marketing and HR specialization The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	2004
Awards	
Awarded the International Advertising Association's Diploma in Marketing Communications	
The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	2007
Bachelor of business Graduated with honours – Magna cum Laude The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	2004
Volunteer experience	